Bishop,
I'm interested in the technology
Raw mentioned in the raw material.
Known as the prana vacuum.
How can we create
a
prana vacuum
using today's technology?
>> The so-called prana vacuum is the same
thing as the idea of what you might call
the quantum vacuum.
It's the same thing as the zero-point
energy concept that many people are
talking about on your planet.
It exists all around you. The technology
exists that you can use to tap into it
in certain ways. Many of the kinds of
things that people have invented that
say it's tapping into the zero-point
energy are not exactly doing so, but the
idea is growing in the consciousness,
the collective consciousness of your
planet until such time as that awareness
evolves into technology that will truly
tap into that prana field, the quantum
field, the void, and whatever else you
may wish to call it.
It will allow you unlimited energy,
unlimited flow,
an inexhaustible supply of energy that
can be utilized in a variety of ways
once you truly tap into that technology.
It has to do with creating devices of
proper resonance, proper frequencies,
capacitors that vibrate at certain
resonant frequencies that deliver and
transform energy in a certain way,
step it down in a way that you can use
with your technology. We have talked a
little bit about this as a space-time
antenna concept, three nested spheres
separated by phi ratio diameters
penetrated by antennae that are
insulated from a merkaba, a double
interpenetrated tetrahedron in the
center of the three spheres that
resonates at certain frequencies and can
be activated by the introduction of
energy into it and it will output energy
of a higher caliber, a higher level and
a higher frequency.
Tapping into the quantum field in
certain ways, but many people on your
planet, a few of them are beginning to
experiment with this and we cannot
deliver more information about this
device until they have already achieved
what it is we have already delivered.
End of discussion.
>> Hello Bashar.
>> Good day.
>> Uh thank you for having this
conversation with each other in this
way.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure to do
so. What would you like to discuss?
>> Talking about the hybrid children, um
you've mentioned in the past that
contact between hybrid children and
their mothers will expand over time.
>> Yes.
>> Has this process indeed started on this
timeline? Is there an Is there an
increase of physical contact between
human beings and the hybrid children?
>> Yes, but in an altered reality, not
necessarily physically on your planet so
much, but in a slightly altered version
of physical reality and in dream time
these encounters have increased.
>> Okay. Wonderful.
>> Eventually, it will leak into the
physical reality as you understand it.
Although it will still be of a higher
vibration than it is now.
>> Yes. Understand. Yeah.
And um I also wanted to talk to you
about suppressed memories.
>> Yes.
>> Um our previous conversation, you've
mentioned
that I was visited by the Grays when I
also was a child.
>> Yes.
>> And that these experiences are buried
deep within my consciousness.
>> Well, not that deep.
>> Oh, not that deep.
>> [laughter]
>> You also mentioned that I felt
victimized because my childlike state
was not able to comprehend what was
going on during these visitations.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And is it correct to say that from
the point of view as a human being child
that these visitations and the removal
of genetic material was somehow
experienced as a trauma on a
psychological level?
>> Yes, but only because of the way you
were raised as a human, not because it's
innate to the being a child, not because
it's innate to being a human child, just
because of the way your planet views
these kinds of things and because it is
short-sighted in its
compartmentalization of awareness.
That's the only reason you experienced
it traumatically.
>> And is that also the reason that what
we're still somehow afraid of
extraterrestrials?
>> Because you are afraid of portions of
your own power and the extraterrestrials
you're encountering represent and
reflect the idea of your true power in
certain ways.
>> Huh, I understand.
And that Yeah, that's probably not a
coincidence, but that leads up to my
next question. Um
Both my parents have transitioned almost
within 3 years of each other and the
last parent, my father, passed 1 year
ago.
>> Yes.
>> And their physical absence caused a
shift in my life.
>> Yes, of course. That's the purpose of
it.
>> Yeah.
Um I experienced this as a tremendous
opportunity to shed a whole bunch of
negative belief systems that I have
bestowed upon myself through their
upbringing.
>> Well, congratulations. That is a
positive way to use it.
>> Thank you.
But I also sense that this tremendous
opportunity is sometimes a bit
frightening.
>> Why?
>> As if this whole new space that has
opened up is sometimes too big to
handle.
>> Impossible.
Otherwise, you wouldn't experience it.
You only grow into the space you're
ready for. So, no matter how it looks,
you're making a comparison still using
some of the outdated beliefs to view it.
Instead of letting go of those outdated
beliefs and understanding you cannot
experience more than you're ready for
anyway.
You can expand into it. That's why it
looks that big because that's how big
you actually are when you let go of the
limiting beliefs.
>> Mhm. I understand what you're saying.
>> All right.
>> what you're saying.
And I also
I'm aware of the physical impact of this
awareness.
>> Yes.
>> Uh
for instance, when my body is sleeping
>> Yes.
>> to respond to this
awareness with an actual physical shock
during the night that eventually wakes
me up.
>> Yes, it can because again
your body's not used to that vibration
or frequency of energy, but it can get
used to it over time.
>> And
how how [clears throat] how can we do
that? Can you say something about
how to to integrate this new space and
the awareness of new space and the
physical response to this? Is it just
going with the flow, letting it happen?
>> That's one way, practice in a sense,
having it happen over and over again,
you'll get used to it. That's one way.
But one way to accelerate that is to
understand or have a perspective
where physical reality isn't really
separate from spirit reality. It's
really not so different. It's just that
you've defined it as very different.
You've placed certain definitions on
physical reality that makes it seem so
unlike spirit reality when in fact it's
a natural extension of it.
>> Okay. And the and the and the and the
physical body that reacts
um
how can we smooth and that out?
>> Well, this is what I'm telling you.
Stop making such a separation in your
belief system between the idea of your
physical body and your spirit.
Your physical body is your spirit in
physical terms.
>> Mhm.
>> It's the same kind of idea, if you wish
a crude analogy, of saying
ice is still water.
It's just frozen.
>> Mhm.
>> But it's the same thing. It's the same
substance, essentially. And so is steam.
So, if you start looking at your body
as if it's simply
euphemistically a frozen version of your
spirit,
or at least a portion of your spirit,
you can start to allow the physical
reality to sort of melt a little bit
more,
>> Mhm.
>> allow it to become a little bit more
fluid, a little bit more liquid, and not
be so different from the liquid version,
or the steam version.
So, you have to start really looking at
physical reality
as if it's just another state of being
of spirit, and not really separate. It's
the idea of separation that's tripping
you up.
>> Yeah, I understand.
Understand.
And um
you also said something about um
that the human beings on Earth will
become more and more human over time.
>> Yes, you're actually not fully human
yet.
>> Yeah, and I was wondering what you meant
by that. What does it mean to be human
as opposed to not being fully human?
>> Being fully human means that you
understand that everything is made of
unconditional love. You understand that
everything is connected, everything is a
reflection of everything else, and you
act accordingly.
>> Mhm.
Yes.
>> Being fully human
is what you ascribe to beings
like Christ, Buddha, Krishna,
so on and so forth.
It's the idea of the behavior that
reflects the godhood within you.
>> Yes.
Yeah.
And that probably also means that
um we're not so compartmentalized
in our way of thinking then.
>> Exactly. You think more holistically,
more as a whole system. That's why I
said you understand everything is one
thing.
I am you from another point of view.
Literally, I am you from another point
of view. You are us from another point
of view.
A fully realized human lives
in that truth.
>> Yeah.
Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> You are so welcome. Aveo.
>> Aveo.
>> Greetings, Bashar.
I have a question for you.
What is the template level of our
space-time reality? You've mentioned
that there is a template level and that
we are each exploring themes
from this template level.
That there is a specific template for
our lives.
I'm wondering if this template is
actually revealed in the deck of what we
consider 52 playing cards.
And if this template level of reality is
expressed, symbolized in the deck of 52
playing cards,
where exactly did these cards come from?
Who created them and when?
And what is the best way for us to
utilize these cards now in our lives in
order to explore the theme of our lives,
play our cards right, and give ourselves
permission
to be our best self. Thanks, Bashar.
>> All 52
are symbolic of the template level
because it can be mixed and match in any
number of ways. It's not any one card,
it's all of them that represents and
symbolizes the template level,
which is created by the choices you make
in spirit to have a physical experience.
So, as above, so below. You use the
energy of the consciousness field to
arrange
certain kinds of blueprints that will
manifest physiologically
as the theme you will explore in
physical reality.
And the idea of any kind of permission
slip like a normal deck of cards or
tarot cards or
any kind of divination system
represents to some degree the idea of
the template level.
Now, you have some freedom in that with
your free will as to how you experience
the template you laid out for yourself,
and sometimes some things can be altered
or shifted.
But in general, the choices made by you
as a spirit will be played out as the
cards you are dealt.
But you can shift them around a little
bit
here and there with your free will. But
you will play that game.
That's what you decided as a spirit.
So, that's how the cards represent the
idea of the template level in energy
that then becomes crystallized down in
frequency, down into what you experience
as the physical card game that you are
playing.
Playing the right cards, as you say, is
easy when you simply follow the formula.
That's the secret to playing your best
hand.
>> Hey, how are you, Michelle?
>> Perfect, and you?
>> Yeah, I'm fine. Uh
let's see. My questions are
um are feelings or thoughts the higher
priority for manifesting our reality?
Because it seems like
uh
unresolved feelings manifest over our
thoughts. So, how are they linked and
>> This is how it works. First, you begin
with beliefs and definitions. What you
believe to be true
is reinforced by the idea of feeling
that it is true, thinking that it is
true, and behaving as if it is true.
Belief systems use feelings, emotions,
thoughts, and behaviors to reinforce the
validity and the reality of the belief
system because physical reality isn't
really real. Therefore, beliefs have to
make you believe that it is real, and
they do so by reinforcing what you
believe to be true with the idea that it
feels true, you think it's true, and you
behave as if it's true. That's the
priority. That's the order in which it
happens. You cannot have a behavior, you
cannot have a thought, and you cannot
have an emotion without first believing
or defining that something is true for
you. Beliefs are the blueprint that
allow you to build the house of your
physical reality. So, it all starts with
that. So, when you behave a certain way,
when you think certain thoughts, when
you feel certain emotions, they all go
back to what must I believe to be true
about myself in order to feel, think,
and behave this way?
Does that help you?
>> Yeah. So, if I want to change the belief
system, the action or how I behave would
be the best way to start and then the
feelings and thoughts would follow?
>> You can start from any direction you
wish, but in a sense, the most efficient
way to change a belief system is to
figure out what that belief is telling
you.
Figure out why you're buying into it
because it may simply be a habit that
you have because you've been taught to
believe this way.
It may be that you're getting something
out of believing that way because you
don't hold on to any belief you don't
think serves you.
So, even if it doesn't seem to serve
you, you may have a belief that says
that the alternative would be worse than
holding on to the beliefs you have even
if they're not comfortable.
Because you all want to believe that
everything needs to serve you, which is
true. It can. But sometimes you have
beliefs
and you hold on to them even if you know
they're not the best beliefs to hold on
to because you have a belief that the
alternative would be worse.
And therefore you'll still hold on to
whatever it is you're holding on to
until you change, until you understand
that the idea that something worse will
happen if you behave more like your true
self is a fallacy. So you have to
examine why the belief is there to begin
with.
Allow yourself to understand why you're
buying into it and be honest in your
self-investigation of what you believe
will happen if you actually go in a
direction you say you would prefer to.
Once you understand that a negative and
fear-based belief is simply telling you
a story that isn't necessarily true,
then you can see that it is nonsensical
and illogical. And as soon as it is
nonsensical, you will drop it because
you don't hold on to things that don't
make sense.
If you do hold on to things that don't
make sense, it's because you have a
belief that says it makes more sense
than the alternative.
>> Mhm.
>> This is what we call the motivational
mechanism in your psychology as humans.
You always, always, without fail
move in the direction of what you
believe serves you. You always, without
fail, move away from what you believe
does not serve you.
So if you see yourself choosing things
that you know, intellectually, don't
serve you, it can only mean you've
defined it and attached a belief to it
that says it's better than the
alternative. It serves you better than
the alternative. Find out why you
believe that and when you expose the
belief and the story it's telling you,
you will see that it makes no sense and
it will be dropped. It will be gone.
>> Okay, thank you.
>> Yes.
>> Um
let's see. The next question is from the
soul's perspective.
Um is the physical body like a
radio-controlled car where you the soul
puts input to make him go left and right
and then there's always input also input
from the environment. So, it's like
>> To some degree, you can use whatever
analogy you wish.
But the idea really is that the physical
world and the physical body is a
projection of the soul's consciousness.
It's like putting on a diving suit. More
than the idea of a remote-controlled
car. It's like putting on a diving suit
or a diving mask and going diving under
the ocean. The mask helps you see
underneath the ocean clearly.
It's not designed to tell you what to
do.
It's designed to tell you what you're
experiencing more clearly.
When you leave the physical reality,
it's like taking off the diving mask and
going back to the surface.
So, even though you have free will as a
physical being, the soul determines what
the general trajectory is from its own
free will. And that may be what the
physical mind thinks of as destiny. In
other words, you are the person you are.
You will do everything as the person you
are. You cannot actually fundamentally
change the person that you are, although
the personality can shift to a great
degree, but it's still happening to you
as you think of yourself as a separate
autonomous being. So, you have the free
will to experience
the destiny of the soul in any way,
shape, or form that the physical mind
chooses to, positive, negative, happy,
sad, whatever, fast, slow, up, down, but
you will walk that path because it was
determined by your free will as a soul.
Is this helping?
>> Yeah, yeah. The diving suit
was a much better
metaphor than the radio control car.
>> All right.
>> Thank you.
Um
two more questions really fast.
>> Yes.
>> Who
when
when a soul wants to have an experience
here on Earth and many souls wants to
have an experience here on Earth,
who gets gets priority?
>> There is no need for priority because
there are a multitude of infinite
parallel realities that can have a
similar experience.
>> Aha.
Okay, and then the last question, on
your planet, do you fart and do you
laugh at your own farts like humans do?
>> We laugh, but we don't eat, so we don't
fart.
>> Okay. Okay.
Yeah,
I think that was all. Thank you very
much.
>> [clears throat]
>> Thank you, Aveo.
>> Aveo.
>> [sighs]
>> Good day, Bashar.
I would like to know about the Bosnian
pyramids, the ones located in Visoko.
Uh
and like who built them and for what
purpose and um
yeah, anything you can tell me about
the pyramids
in Visoko, Bosnia.
Thank you.
>> Pyramids around your planet
at a certain time were all built
relatively close to one another in time.
Around your 10,500 years ago.
The idea is that they were energy
collectors to balance the Earth that had
gone through a catastrophic change when
it was impacted by commentary body that
caused the annihilation of your
Atlantean civilization.
And therefore, knowledge and energy was
preserved in many pyramids around the
planet. And also, they were used as an
energy balancing system to bring the
planet back into alignment, so it could
recuperate and heal.
There are other things that they were
used for, but we will not go into that
right now.
>> Hello, Bashar.
>> And to you, good day.
>> I'm very excited to be here. Thank you
for for talking to me.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure. What
would you like to discuss?
>> Um so, I've been I've been following my
excitement more and more since I kind of
started to listen to to you speak. And
I've It feels really great, and I I've
been doing some like bigger and some
smaller changes, and I'm
I'm following your advice of listening
of
basically following my excitement more
moment to moment, because there's no
like one big thing in that sense.
>> All right. Now, do you remember the
entire formula, not just follow your
excitement? There's other pieces to it,
yes?
>> Yes. Yes, I know.
>> Um
and I um
I think what I'm
like one thing that just as an as an
example that I I I was I quit one one
job that I I felt like I was not excited
about at all.
Um and now I have more free time, which
is fun.
Um and then sometimes I
I I get kind of frustrated with myself,
because I I feel like I sit there and I
have I know that I have all these
options
to to act on, but I don't I kind of
don't know what to do. And I wonder if
>> Yes, you do. Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
The idea, again, isn't that complicated.
Don't overcomplicate it. If you have
different options,
decide for yourself which one is not
only more attractive, more exciting than
any other option, but which one can you
act on? Which one can you do something
about? If it seems that more than one is
equal,
you might as well flip a coin.
Remember, synchronicity comes to bear in
this because if you flip a coin and say,
"All right, heads option A, tails option
B."
And you flip the coin, one of two things
might happen.
Let's say
it lands on tails, option B.
And you find yourself going, "Oh,
goody."
Or you find yourself going, "Oh, I wish
it had been option A instead. Oh, I wish
it had been option A." Then you will
know that that was the one that was more
exciting. Or if you do head down a path
that isn't necessarily the most exciting
path for you at that moment,
synchronicity will create certain
circumstances that will turn you around
in the correct direction. That's how it
works. It's an automatic mechanism. So,
you don't have to sit there and wonder
and wonder and be frustrated. Just act
on whatever you are capable of acting on
that contains more excitement than
anything else as far as you can
determine, and let synchronicity guide
you with the red light, green light
aspect of its being, of its nature,
which means it will bring you
opportunities you can act on and take
further, green light synchronicity. It
will prevent you from acting on certain
things that are not the correct path for
you right now, red light synchronicity.
Just like you follow your traffic lights
when you drive. You understand?
>> Mhm.
>> So, the starting and stopping is the way
synchronicity guides you. No, not right
now. Don't act in that direction. Act in
this direction. Whatever you can act on.
And you have to use your imagination. Be
very creative about the idea of what it
means to take action on something in
every way that you possibly can that has
to do with that thing you say excites
you. Even if you have to simulate the
reality, that's taking an action on it.
>> Mhm.
>> Let me give you an example that many
people on your planet have used.
There are many people who you call
celebrities that are famous.
But you will hear stories from many of
them that before they were actually able
to literally do what it is that they now
do that they're famous for,
they acted it out. They simulated it.
Even sometimes going so far
for someone who might be a public
speaker in an auditorium or a game show
host or a late night interviewer as to
go into a space, set it up like it's
really happening, even to the level of
putting fake people in the audience,
maybe even just cardboard cutouts, and
doing their routine as if it's really
happening. Because then you're training
your body to get used to the vibration
of the reality of that, and that will
make you attracted more strongly. By
doing anything you can to simulate
anything you can to take an action in
the direction of what excites you more
than any other choice. And when we talk
about that, it can also be very simple
things. We don't mean when we say follow
your passion, follow your excitement,
that it has to be a grand project or
come with trumpets or be a life-spanning
career. Ta-da! Here's your passion. No.
Every day you have little options,
simple options. I can take a walk. I can
read a book. I can have lunch with a
friend. I can watch a movie.
Just choose the one that has more
attractiveness, more curiosity, more
excitement, even just a tiniest bit more
that you're able to act on than any
other one, and just do that first.
You're still following your excitement
by doing it on that level, and
eventually it will usually snowball
through synchronicity to bring you more
and more opportunities to act on your
passion in bigger and bigger and bigger
ways. But, the point is it doesn't
really matter if it does or not because
you're still following your excitement
just by making sure that every day the
options you choose are more exciting
than any other option, and taking action
on the ones that you can. That's all
there is to it. You don't have to make
it a big mystery or overcomplicated or
overthink it. That's why you're
frustrated.
>> So, you're saying I'm frustrated because
I am making it way more complicated.
>> Yes.
>> Cuz I feel like sometimes it's it's
literally that I have like an afternoon
off and I'm sitting at home and I I I I
I don't know like I'm I I I
>> Then, you're not using your creative
imagination.
Sitting at home. Why are you speaking
with us today? Was this more exciting
than any other option?
>> Yes.
>> Well, you see that wasn't hard.
So, what will you do after this
conversation is over? What are your
options after this conversation is over?
What are your options? Name some.
>> Um probably
go to sleep because it's quite late
here.
>> All right, going to sleep can be
exciting. That's fine. But, let's say
it's morning. What would be some of your
options?
>> Um I usually like
go for walk, go to work out.
>> Do you enjoy those things? Are they
expressions of your passion?
>> I Yes, they are.
>> Are you sure cuz you kind of hesitated.
>> No, I'm sure.
>> All right, because remember sometimes
you may be sort of doing what excites
you, but you may not be doing it in the
most exciting way
because the idea of following your
passion
requires every component of it to also
be the most exciting way. So, you can do
a thing,
but where you're doing it, how you're
doing it, when you're doing it, with
whom you're doing it, all have to be of
that vibration, or you're not really
following your passion.
So, you get to decide the way in which
you're actually acting on your
excitement.
And isn't that an exciting thought?
>> It is actually.
>> All right. So, just make sure that
whatever is you choose to do out of the
options that you have, whether it's
taking a walk or working out, you're
doing it in the most exciting way as a
whole system. All the components of it
are being done in the most exciting way.
And if you can't find that one of the
components is the most exciting way you
would prefer to do it,
invent, use your creative imagination to
create your exciting way of doing it.
Yes?
>> Mhm.
Yeah, I think that that what you just
said with the creative
Yeah, that that actually helps a lot.
I've never thought about it that way,
but I have the power to do that.
>> You do.
You do.
So,
if that makes things more exciting, then
you're on the right path.
>> Yeah.
>> Does this help?
>> Yeah, that that helped a lot. Yes, it
really did.
>> All right. Does that serve you today?
>> Yes.
>> Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> Then we thank you for your interaction.
Aveo.
>> Thank you. Have a great day.
>> Of course, always. You too.
>> [laughter]
>> Thanks.
Bye.
>> Why would I have anything else?
>> Sorry?
>> Why would I choose anything else?
>> Oh, yeah. That's makes sense.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, I know. That's why I said it.
So, go
>> I see.
>> and don't choose
what doesn't make sense.
>> I will. Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> It's up to you. Thank you.